getcu3er.com 2011-10-06

# Privacy Policy - CU3ER

MADEBYPLAY d.o.o. (“MADEBYPLAY”) respect your right to privacy and feel it is important for You to know how we handle the information we receive from You via our website at [http://getcu3er.com](http://getcu3er.com/) (the “Site”) and through our tools and services offered on the Site (the “Service”). 

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, MADEBYPLAY collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. MADEBYPLAY’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how MADEBYPLAY’s visitors use the Site. From time to time, MADEBYPLAY may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Site. 

MADEBYPLAY also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. MADEBYPLAY does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Site choose to interact with MADEBYPLAY in ways that require MADEBYPLAY to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that MADEBYPLAY gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at [http://getcu3er.com](http://getcu3er.com/) to provide a email address. Those who engage in transactions with MADEBYPLAY – by purchasing CU3ER PRO license and access to the CU3ER account , for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. 

In each case, MADEBYPLAY collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with MADEBYPLAY. MADEBYPLAY does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

MADEBYPLAY may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. MADEBYPLAY may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, MADEBYPLAY does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

MADEBYPLAY discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on MADEBYPLAY’s behalf or to provide services available at MADEBYPLAY’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Site, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. MADEBYPLAY will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, MADEBYPLAY discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when MADEBYPLAY believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of MADEBYPLAY, third parties or the public at large. 

MADEBYPLAY uses a third-party intermediary to manage credit card processing and this intermediary is not permitted to store, retain, or use Your billing information except to process Your credit card information for MADEBYPLAY.

If you are a registered user of Site and have supplied your email address, MADEBYPLAY may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Site and MADEBYPLAY products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or ticket via one of our feedback/support mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. MADEBYPLAY takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. MADEBYPLAY uses cookies to help MADEBYPLAY identify and track visitors, their usage of Site, and their website access preferences. MADEBYPLAY visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using MADEBYPLAY’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of MADEBYPLAY’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

MADEBYPLAY may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in MADEBYPLAY’s sole discretion. MADEBYPLAY encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a CU3ER account, you should also check your account page for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Terms of Service

When You access and use the Service, You are subject to the MADEBYPLAY [Terms Of Service](http://getcu3er.com/terms). 

### Contact Us

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please [contact us](http://getcu3er.com/contact).
